wholesaledir.com 2011-12-31

# 

## Wholesale Directory - wwww.wholesaledir.com - Privacy Policy...

**Privacy Policy for** **The Wholesale Directory - www.wholesaledir.com** ****

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us with the information provided at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. 

At www.wholesaledir.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. Our Privacy Policy is Reviewed and Verified for Accuracy via Regular Basis. 

We have outlined below what types of personal information are received and collected by www.wholesaledir.com and how it is used. ******_What Information We May Collect from Web Log Files_ -**

Like many other Web sites, our Wholesale Directory - www.wholesaledir.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

Newsletters and Subscriptions of Services - "Opt-In" - Newsletters & Special Offers -   
If a new or returning user to www.wholesaledir.com wishes to subscribe to our Newsletter or Special Email Product/Service Offers from our "Affiliated Content Network," we may additionally request and collect "A Visitor's" First/Last Name & Email Address. Out of respect for our users privacy, we always provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Additionally, we do not share, abuse or compromise any personal information "Opt-in" Email Newsletter/Special-Offer(s) Subscribers List(s).

**_Paid Subscriptions, Memberships and Services_** -

With respect to Online Payments and Billing Information: We have appropriate, up-to date and Tested Security measures in place via online secure payment gateway, as well as in our physical office facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the following email Address: Contact [at] wholesaledir.com. _**Cookies and Web Beacons**_ \-   
www.wholesaledir.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Additionally, several of the companies who may have "Products and Service(s) + Company Listings/Advertisements placed with in our extensive Wholesalers Directory - www.wholesaledir.com, may also use "Cookies" in order to gauge their sales promotions, market share and overall demographics of the visitors preferred or sent to their Web site.

You should know that third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served from this site. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve contextual ads to the user  on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve contextual ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.wholesaledir.com.   
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.wholesaledir.com and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners may include such companies as....   
Google Adsense   
Commission Junction   
Clickbank 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.wholesalerc.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.wholesaledir.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.wholesalerc.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**  
**

**

Please feel free to contact us Directly with any additional questions, concerns and/or observations with respect to the Previously Mentioned Privacy Policy for The Wholesale Resource Center - www.wholesalerc.com. 

**The Online Wholesale Directory - www.wholesaledir.com**

**Contact [at] Wholesaledir.com**

**7491 N. Federal Hwy. C-5 Suite 298**

**Boca Raton, FL 33487**

**561-498-5275 (Phone) - & \- 561-498-5905 (Fax)**

**
